<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gesblue</string>
    <string name="butlletaImpresaOk_enviar">No</string>
    <string name="butlletaImpresaOk_imprimir">Yes</string>
    <string name="butlleta">BULLETIN</string>
    <string name="butlletaDeDenuncia">" Bulletin of complaint"</string>
    <string name="butlletaEnviadaOk">" Bulletin routed properly. You desire to print a copy?"</string>
    <string name="butlletaEnviadaOk_acceptar">" Accept"</string>
    <string name="butlletaEnviadaOk_cancelar">" Cancel"</string>
    <string name="butlletaImpresaOk">" Bulletin printed properly. You want to print another copy?"</string>
    <string name="textPeu">Notification of the complaint and initiation of the procedure: les \n 
        We notify this complaint as the infringing vehicle holder
        \n reviewed on the back and let them know what\'s left
        \n initiated the corresponding sanctioning procedure.
        \n \n In case you were not the driver, you are required to
        \n that within 15 business days following the
        \n date of receipt of this notification proceed to identify
        \n to the driver responsible for the offense against which he
        \n will initiate the sanctioning procedure. \n \n

        Abbreviated procedure and ordinary procedure: If desired
        \n accept the processing of this file by procedure
        \n abbreviated, it has a period of 20 calendar days to count
        \n from the day after this notification to make the
        \n payment of the amount of the penalty indicated in the complaint, with a
        \n 50 \%% discount. This procedure implies: the waiver of
        \n make claims, the completion of the procedure without
        \n need to issue an express resolution and the certainty of the
        \n penalty from the first moment of payment. In case of no
        \n make the payment with the discount of 50 \%% continue the
        \n processing by the procedure from the day after the
        \n notification. These must be presented at the OAC of
        \n Banyoles Town Hall. If you do not make claims or pay the
        \n sanction amount this complaint will have the effect of minutes
        \n resolution of the sanctioning procedure. Against the penalty is
        \n It may file an appeal for replacement within one month.
        \n \n For the processing of the sanctioning procedure will act as
        \n Instructor body of the file the Chief of the Local Police
        \n the City Council of \n being the competent body for its resolution This Corporation.
        \n \n Payment of the fine: Presenting this newsletter to any cashier
        \n automatic open line or office of \\ \"la caixa \\\". \n \n The secretary of the City Council.</string>


    <string-array name="Idiomes">
        <item>Catalan</item>
        <item>Spanish</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>French</item>
        <item>German</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="NO">NO</string>
    <string name="SI">YES</string>
    <string name="titol_data">DATE</string>
    <string name="titol_hora">TIME</string>
    <string name="titol_matricula">LICENSE PLATE</string>
    <string name="zona">ZONE</string>
    <string name="usuari">USER</string>
    <string name="cela_fetDenunciat">" FACT DENOUNCED"</string>
    <string name="cela_identificacio">" IDENTIFICATION"</string>
    <string name="cela_color">COLOUR</string>
    <string name="cela_codi_anulacio">" CODE ANNULMENT"</string>
    <string name="cela_agent">AGENT</string>
    <string name="carrer">" STREET"</string>
    <string name="cela_dataLimit">DEADLINE ANNULMENT</string>
    <string name="cela_dataLimitPagamentAmbAquestDoc">" Borderline day payment with this doc.:"</string>
    <string name="color">COLOUR</string>
    <string name="cela_pagamentEntitatBancaria">" PAYMENT AT BANKING ENTITY"</string>
    <string name="cela_referencia">REFERENCE</string>
    <string name="cela_vehicle">" VEHICLE"</string>
    <string name="cela_marcaIModel">BRAND AND MODEL</string>
    <string name="cela_llocInfraccio">" PLACE OF THE INFRACTION"</string>
</resources>